

JESSICA HUE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER | MARGARET BUJ

OBJECTIVE

HTML5, IBM Cloud, and Multiplatform Mobile App full stack developer with 3+ years of professional experience. Skilled with WordPress, JavaScript, PHP, and SQL and demonstrating a strong ability to improve software efficiency by over 20%.

SKILLS

Javascript | HTML | PHP |
Python | Problem Solving |
Cross- team communication |
SQL databases | Wordpress |
Kentico | Drupal

EXPERIENCE

HUMPHREY INC—FUCK STACK DEVELOPER - NEWARK, NJ — 2019 - 2020

Scrum Master of 5-person team. Introduced 3-tier architecture on company website and applications.

Applied new data processing systems for SQL databases that improved efficiency by over 20% and saved \$350,000 per year.

TRAYTON TECHNOLOGIES — JR FUCK STACK DEVELOPER – NEW YORK CITY, NY — 2017 – 2018

Found and repaired over 300 bugs on software systems.

Worked closely with the UX team to optimize JavaScript and PHP codes, improving latency and user journey.

Implemented improvement to WordPress CMS systems to increase ease of use for stakeholders.

Introduced new security measures in SQL databases, reducing the risk of data theft by 35%.

EDUCATION

BSC SORFTWARE PROGRAMMING – UNIVERSITY OF SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA – LOS ANGELES, CA – 2017 – 2020

Made the Dean's List in 2019 Achieved a 3.9 GPA Relevant coursework: Java Programming, Operating System Architecture, SQL Database design, CMS Architecture Management

CERTIFICATIONS

HTML 5 web developer

Camp Certificate IBM Full Stack Cloud Developer Certificate
Full Stack Web and Multplatform Mobile App Development Certificate







